yourfinancebook.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Your Finance Book

Privacy of our visitors are important to us. We at yourfinancebook.com collects information when you fill out a form or comments on our site. These information are used  to personalize your experience and to improve our customer service. We do not sell, trade, exchange or transfer any of these information to outside parties for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ "Ad settings of google").

We use third party advertisement on our site. All most all the advertisers uses technology such as cookies, web beacon etc for advertising in our site and it will send certain information such as your IP address, internet service provider name etc. You can disable cookies from your browser settings.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and understand your preference when you visit our site.

We may collect, use or record your personal information to help us work and provide you better service. We do not sell your personal information collected from our website to third parties for their use. We can use personal information gathered from our site only to follow up and with no other intention or use.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy then you many contact us by filling out the form below.
